and it's time to get into the big up let down are y'all ready our big up goes to wig support
and sisterhood so there was a basketball game between the university of mississippi rebels
and south carolina gamecock now guard markeisha davis fell and the unthinkable happened the six
foot basketball stars wig came flying off during the fall and in a moment of indubitable solidarity
davis's teammates and members of the south carolina uh gamecocks crowded around her
to shield her and the detached hair piece until they got it back in place now this is what black
history month is all about madam cj walker would be proud also can we get that baby some baby some
bobby pins or some gorilla glue like we got to do something to keep that wig on y'all now our let
down let down and it goes to the sanctity of black history month i just feel like during black history
month everything should be peaches and cream no 112 or maybe yes 112 since it's black history month i
feel like even the bloods and crips should be like during black history month we don't squabble we
don't got no beefs no nothing all black on black crime should go down during black history month
and so should black on black shade people going on club shay shay and just airing it out airing it out
then you got meg the stallion versus nikki minaj i mean jay-z versus the grammys which really isn't
black on black anything because there ain't nobody over there doing what they need to be doing
let's all tighten up we still got a few weeks left all right